Guide to the Papers of the Cavendish-Talbot Family Folger MS X.d.428 (1-203)
Folger Shakespeare Library
- Cavendish-Talbot family papers, 1548-1607; Series 1; X.d.428 (1-147)
  - Correspondence, 1.1
    - Letter from Richard Grey, Tutbury, to George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, 1584? November 28; X.d.428 (33)
      At the last audit at Tutbury, the auditor and receiver examined the locks of the castle gates. Postern gates were nailed up in their presence.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/j6n5ue
    - Letter from James Hardwick, Hardwick, to Lady Elizabeth St. Loe, ca. 1564 or 1565 December 1; X.d.428 (34)
      Informs his sister of business relating to a recognizance. His cousin Willoughby has married Mr. Littleton's (Lytelltons) daughter, of Worcestershire(?).
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/zv390a
    - Letter from James Hardwick, Hardwick, to Lady Elizabeth St. Loe, ca. 1565 January 20; X.d.428 (35)
      Business matters.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/1gk70o
    - Letter from James Hudson, London, to Lady Arabella Stuart, at court, 1605/6 February 24; X.d.428 (36)
      The bearer, Richard Lassye, is the poor man she has been so long desirous of helping.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/qn0nux
    - Letter from Henry Hastings, Earl of Huntingdon, York, to Avery Copley and Robert Key, 1589 December 15; X.d.428 (37)
      Asks them on his behalf to arbitrate between Mr. John Lacy and Jesper and Hugh Blithman.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/qqqb90
    - Letter from Susan (Bertie) Grey, Countess of Kent, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1592/3 January 26; X.d.428 (38)
      Recommends the bearer as a porter to her aunt. Apologizes for not writing in her own hand, but her finger continues so evil so that she cannot hold a pen.
      Written from "my howse."
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/9e7i9n
    - Letter from John Kniveton, Shrewsbury Place, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1579 December 23; X.d.428 (39)
      Has delivered the venison and round pies to Mr. Attorney and the others. The pies that were made "longewayes" were so little and moldy that they were not worth giving and in the future should be "newe baked," and "made of some reasonable bignes and well handled." Gives news of the trial held to try and settle a dispute about encroachments in the Duchy of Lancaster. Even though he had testified against the inhabitants, Mr. Sackford advised that she and her husband make sure that the "inhabitantes abowt the fforrest were well vsed," because he had heard some "very evill speaches of my Lord in the courte." (see R. Somerville, History of the Duchy of Lancaster (1953), p. 306-308.)
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/809t5g
    - Letter from William Kniveton, from court, to Mrs. Jane Kniveton, Hardwick, 1604 May 27; X.d.428 (40)
      Informs his mother that the plague has not increased in London. The Duke of Florence sent gifts to the king, queen, and prince. Mentions a recent wedding. Lady Arbella asked him to commend her to his mother.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/bt1eh1
    - Letter from William Kniveton, from court, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, Hardwick, 1607 June 22; X.d.428 (41)
      Some enclosures near Lincoln were thrown open by certain unruly persons. Parliament sits with little to do. A new Lord Chief Justice of England (Sir Thomas Fleming) and Lord Chief Baron (Justice Tanfield) were named. The King will soon go to Theobalds, and then the Isle of Wight, on a progress. The King has placated the Lord Treasurer with a diamond.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/12id2r
    - Letter from William Kniveton, Mercaston (Myrcaston), Derbyshire, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, Hardwick, 1607 December 31; X.d.428 (42)
      Sends New Year's greetings.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/v5bam2
    - Letter from Thomas Knyvets, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1573? November 7; X.d.428 (43)
      Sir Valentine Browne wrote to him from Berwick of the delivery of some prisoners taken at the capture of Edinburgh castle. May be some question of the safety of Shrewsbury's charge.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/3m8ls4
    - Letter from Nicholas Kynnersley, Wingfield, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1588 November 5; X.d.428 (44)
      Refers to the differences between the Earl and herself. Advises her not to absent herself any longer. Lady Arbella was merry this evening, and ate her meat.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/f7sx10
    - Letter from Nicholas Kynnersley, Wingfield, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1589 April 22; X.d.428 (45)
      Encloses part of her principal jewels. She shall find all things at Wingfield in good order.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/q82a6b
    - Letter from Sir? Francis Leake, Sutton, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, ca. 1578? April 8; X.d.428 (46)
      Mentions to his sister-in-law his disputed title to the lands he lately purchased from the Earl of Leicester, formerly part of the monastery of Croxton.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/4yr288
    - Letter from Elizabeth (Leake) Leche, Harstoft, Derbyshire, to Elizabeth Leche, ca. 1560 November 11; X.d.428 (47)
      Informs her daughter that "my dowghteres Sayntloo" children and "my son Knystones" children are merry and in good health. She has sent some of her daughters to Chatsworth because the pox are rife in her neighbor's houses, while other daughters are still with her until the sickness is past. Asks about the health of other children.
      Martinmas day.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/q21t93
    - Letter from Elizabeth (Leake) Leche, to Lady Elizabeth St. Loe, ca. 1565; X.d.428 (48)
      Thanks her daughter for the kindness shown to her daughter Margaret. Asks her to lend her son so much money as a certain piece of land is worth because he is in immediate need of money.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/sc3bi0
    - Letter from Robert Dudley, Earl of Leicester, to George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, 1571? December 16; X.d.428 (49)
      Expresses his affection to his kinsman and his desire to serve him, and assures him of the Queen's good opinion of him. The Spanish ambassador is commanded to depart the realm.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/i25753
    - Letter from Elizabeth Stuart, Countess of Lennox, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, Hardwick, before 1574 October; X.d.428 (50)
      Thanks her for lending her the litter for her journey.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/qt93ja
    - Letter from Elizabeth Stuart, Countess of Lennox, Hackney, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1577? July 25; X.d.428 (51)
      Begs her mother to no longer "exteme" such false bruits about her.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/kp6vyh
    - Letter from John Lenton, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1571 August 12; X.d.428 (52)
      Reports on a dispute over land involving herself and others in which he is trying to act as an intermediary. Refers to her husband as "my Lorde your Beadfelow." Beseeches her to use the young gentleman, Master Pierrepont (Perpoynte), "as gently as ye can, that we may wynne hym." Has heard that Anne Perpont? is in love with one Texle; if this be so then the hope of Mr. Chaworth "that wayse ys dawnted." Master Perpont? has a book of his called "Gallen in Phesycke." Her two sweet children are in health. P.S., a proverb: "by close dealyng, a man may come to a kyngdom."
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/855rig
    - Letter from Sir John Manners, Haddon, to William Cavendish, Hardwick, 1598 December 6; X.d.428 (53)
      Asks after all at Hardwick, including Lady Arbella Stuart. Perhaps he would like to join him and others in procuring a pardon for Hollyngworth and Stafford condemned for the burglary in Glossopdale.
      Inside: Cavendish drafts his reply stating that he has returned the supplication to which he has set his hand.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/7q2xv6
    - Letter from Sir John Manners, Haddon, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, Hardwick, 1602 December 21; X.d.428 (54)
      Answers her letter on behalf of Sir Edward Dyer.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/4911x8
    - Letter from Sir John Manners, Haddon, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, Hardwick, 1604 June 18; X.d.428 (55)
      Thanks her for her good wishes on the birth of this child, (his grandson John Manners, later 8th Earl of Rutland, b. June 10, 1604), and seeks her advice concerning the christening.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/rw5fzl
    - Letter from Roger Manners, Kynnolton (Kinoulton), Nottinghamshire, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, Hardwick, 1597 August 11; X.d.428 (56)
      On behalf of the bearer thanks her for her favor.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/w9qr7x
    - Letter from William Marchington, Chatsworth, to Lady Elizabeth St. Loe, ca. 1560 January 13; X.d.428 (57)
      Reports on the children and matters concerning the Chatsworth estate--hedges, marble, orchards, and cattle. Has sent four pots with the carrier of this letter. Wishes "all my lyttell mistres encrease of learning which I trust to see." P.S., James Crompe was at Derby.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/4y5i59
    - Letter from Christopher Michell, Sheffield, to George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, ca. 1579 or 1580? August 11; X.d.428 (58)
      Has not been able fully to conclude with his tenants.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/179vob
    - Letter from James Montagu, from court, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1605/6 February 10; X.d.428 (59)
      It is a very joyful matter to see how well the king, his lords, and commons do agree together in this parliament, particularly in the need to have some "seuere execution vppon the preests and recusants for the late executions of the traytors" (after the Gunpowder Plot). Henry Garnet or Walley has been apprehended.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/h6998r
    - Letter from James Montagu, the court at Whitehall, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, Hardwick, 1605/6 March 7; X.d.428 (60)
      The news here is all in parliament business (after the Gunpowder Plot.) Garnet is in the Tower, and the Earl of Northumberland is expected to be cleared. More arraignments are expected. The queen "groweth bigg."
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/f90dlr
    - Letter from William Moulso, London, to Lady Elizabeth St. Loe, 1564? December 14; X.d.428 (61)
      Announces the birth of a son to Lady Cobham (Henry, 11th baron, born November 22), and other court news. (See X.d.428 (16)).
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/v0j1ti
    - Letter from Mary Percy, Countess of Northumberland, Broomhall (Bromehall), Yorkshire, to Lady Elizabeth Cavendish, ca. 1555 May 27; X.d.428 (62)
      Asks for the restoration of certain cattle and land to the bearer and another.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/4ob3fw
    - Letter from Thomas Butler, Earl of Ormonde, Dublin, to Sir William St. Loe, captain of the Queen's guard, ca. 1560? January 29; X.d.428 (63)
      Is anxious for news of him. Hopes that even though he is out of sight he is not out of mind. Lord Sussex is sick of an ague.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/399ydw
    - Letter from John Parker, Dublin Castle, to Thadeus O'Carroll (Okewell, Okarell), 1548 November 23; X.d.428 (64)
      Informs him of the Lord Deputy's wish to educate his son, an ex-hostage, in his (the lord deputy's) household and of the advantages of such an upbringing.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/k9b7kn
    - Letter from William Herbert, Earl of Pembroke, Baynard's Castle, London, to Sir William St. Loe, 1548 or 1549 February 6; X.d.428 (65)
      St. Loe is to deliver one Gilbert, sometime servant to Sir Thomas Darcye, and now serving under St. Loe in Ireland, to the bearer.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/k0qcm9
    - Letter from William Herbert, Earl of Pembroke, from court, to George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, 1567/8 February 22; X.d.428 (66)
      Refers to the forthcoming sale of Shrewsbury's manor of Stockterden.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/889ek3
    - Letter from Lady Frances Pierrepont, Holme, Pierrepont, Nottinghamshire, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, ca. 1575; X.d.428 (67)
      The letter accompanies New Year's gifts to her mother: a piece of lawn and a drinking glass.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/03o32h
    - Letter from Lady Frances Pierrepont to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1603 April; X.d.428 (68)
      A recent visitor, Sir John Hales, says that his majesty will be at Berwick Saturday next. He says all things in the Southern parts proceed peaceably, and hopes that (Edward Seymour) Lord Beauchamp's assemblies will dissolve into smoke.
      Early April 1603.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/24as9j
    - Letter from Sir George Pierrepont, Woodhouse, to Lady Elizabeth St. Loe, 1561 November 4; X.d.428 (69)
      Mentions his suit and the projected match between her daughter and his son (Frances and Henry.)
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/wcb72d
    - Letter from Sir George Pierrepont, Holme, Pierrepont, Nottinghamshire, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, Chatsworth, 1562 May 18; X.d.428 (70)
      Further discussion concerning the match, a visit to Chatsworth, and the articles of agreement.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/dwi1w0
    - Letter from Edward Manners, Earl of Rutland, Newark, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, ca. 1570 April 18; X.d.428 (71)
      Requests her to consider favorably the claim of his kinswoman, an old servant of the late countess, her predecessor, to a piece of land.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/u51tw9
    - Letter from Roger Manners, Earl of Rutland, Belvoir (Biluoire), Leicestershire, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1606 October 13; X.d.428 (72)
      Thanks her for her kindness to his cousin, Mr. Edward Talbot.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/uksvw8
    - Warrant from Sir Richard Sackville, Sackville Place, London, to Sir John Byron, 1565 August 10; X.d.428 (73)
      Warrant authorizing Lady St. Loe to have certain game from the park of Clipstone, Nottinghamshire, where he (Byron) is master of the game.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/792mbu
    - Letter from Margaret St. Loe to Lady Elizabeth St. Loe, 1560? June 13; X.d.428 (74)
      Has heard of her son Edward's plot to poison Lady Elizabeth and Lady Elizabeth's husband.
    - Letter from Sir William St. Loe, Windsor, to Lady Elizabeth St. Loe, 1560? September 4; X.d.428 (75)
      General news. "The qvene yesterdaye her owne seylff rydeng apon the waye craved my horse, vnto home I gave hym." The almoner (of Eton) says that no gentlemen's boys in England shall be better welcome than their boys.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/b2d77o
    - Letter from Sir William St. Loe, Master Man's house in Red Cross Street, London, to Lady Elizabeth St. Loe, Chatsworth, ca. 1560 October 12; X.d.428 (76)
      Has leave to come and wait upon her, so will respond to her letters in person.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/h82y0l
    - Letter from Sir William St. Loe, London, to Lady Elizabeth St. Loe, Chatsworth, ca. 1560 October 24; X.d.428 (77)
      Addressed to "My honest swete Chatesworth." Asks her to send linens for his use at Whitehall. Complains about the servants at Chatsworth, and his aching teeth. The Queen has found fault with his long absence, to which he replied to the Queen that when she understood the truth and cause she would not be offended, to which she replied, "verye well very well sowbeytt hand off hers did I nott kysse." Other news.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/48o330
    - Letter from unidentified correspondent, Carige, to Lady Elizabeth St. Loe, 1564 October 22; X.d.428 (78)
      He (another William St. Loe, not Lady Elizabeth's husband) has been travailing in her matters. He is glad that she is in good health, and trusts that the near completion of Chatsworth will continue her health. She should forbear Sir William St. Loe more than she has. Salutes her brother and sister Kniveton.
      Illegible signature of correspondent.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/pf178h
    - Letter from Sir George Savile, bart., Thornhill, to Avery Copley, Craven, Yorkshire, 1592/3 January 26; X.d.428 (79)
      He has been persuaded to stand as one of the knights of the shire this next parliament and asks for his good help in Craven.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/il2b84
    - Letter from Richard Savile, Thornhill, to William Ryche, Tankersley, Yorkshire, ca. 1575?; X.d.428 (80)
      Notice to be ready with his draughts to plough.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/qk6v13
    - Letter from Edward Talbot, Bothell, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, Hardwick, 1604 May 12; X.d.428 (81)
      Informs his stepmother of the sorry state of his brother-in-law Henry's finances, and of words spoken privately to Edward's servant by his sister and Henry's wife Grace, "which he [the servant] thought should not haue proceded from hir."
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/sa4y39
    - Letter from Lady Elizabeth Cavendish, London, to Francis Whitfield, Chatsworth, 1552? November 14; X.d.428 (82)
      Whitfield should look well to all things at Chatsworth until her aunt (Marcella Linacre) arrives, and cause Bronshawe to look to things at Pentrich. Lists specific tasks: restocking of beer, charcoal, and wood, improvements to be made in her bedchamber, and provision for her sister Jane's needs.
      On overleaf, a note of things to do in another hand.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/1t248i
    - Letter from Lady Elizabeth St. Loe, from court, to James Crompe, 1560? March 8; X.d.428 (83)
      Worth, who says he will depart at Ladyday next, must be bound in an obligation; he lies like a false knave. Directions for the employment of certain builders at Pentrich, Medowpleck, and Chatsworth. She perceives that Sir James is much disliked for his religion but she thinks his wisdom is such that he will make small account of that matter. Tell her aunt Linacre to have the little garden by the new house made a garden this year. The carrier of this letter also brings three bundles of garden seeds.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/d2o9uh
    - Letter from Lady Elizabeth St. Loe to Francis Whitfield, ca. 1560 October 20; X.d.428 (84)
      Instructions for the erection of the battlement at Chatsworth. P.S. "tyll besse knolles and franke thatt I saye yf they pley their uergenalles [virginals] that the[y] are good gerles."
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/km0948
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, Wingfield, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1568? June 28; X.d.428 (85)
      Hopes to be with her at Chatsworth late tomorrow. Thanks her for the bacon and capon.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/p1q6e0
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, Hampton Court, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, Tutbury, 1568 December; X.d.428 (86)
      Has received her letter of December 1. Thanks her for her puddings and venison. The plague is in London. Her majesty declared that before long he should well perceive she did so trust him as she did few, which he doubts is in reference to the custody of the Scots queen.
      Early December 1568
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/85ct6i
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, from court, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, Tutbury, 1568 December 13; X.d.428 (87)
      Has received her letter of December 8. Discusses land leases. Reports that lord Sheffield and Lady Paget have died. "Your blake man is in helthe." P.S. Now it is certain the Scots queen comes to Tutbury to his charge.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/45xa43
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, Wingfield, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1569?; X.d.428 (88)
      He is so busy that he will not suffer the gout to settle itself in him.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/1roxn1
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, ca. 1570; X.d.428 (89)
      Refers to a lady's correspondence (Mary, Queen of Scots?). He likes his wife's letters so well that he has sent them to Gilbert.
      (Hunter dates it 1573?)
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/8934vp
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, Sheffield Castle, to his "good lordship", 1571 September 30; X.d.428 (90)
      A request to help his cousin Vernon enter into the inheritance of Sir George Vernon, deceased.
      Unsigned draft.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/6734w3
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, ca. 1571; X.d.428 (91)
      Mentions a possible pursuivantship for Anthony Barlow.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/qx0m1a
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, ca. 1571; X.d.428 (92)
      Has delivered 20 of the 34 dozen (does not say what) of him to the Scots queen.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/k94pvm
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1574? Spring; X.d.428 (93)
      Has sent her Thomas Kniveton's letter that she may peruse what is bruited of the young king.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/76a19q
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1574? Spring; X.d.428 (94)
      John Kniveton came yesterday and brought papers and no money. Her plate is not come down according to her promise. The house is greatly troubled with the measles.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/034eh0
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, Sheffield, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1574 August 8; X.d.428 (95)
      He has fulfilled her various commissions.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/bqo7r4
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, Sheffield, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, 1575 June 7; X.d.428 (96)
      Discusses the problem of the Peak's men. Will provide plate for Gilbert. She should do something about Charles's escapades.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/316d35
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, ca. 1575; X.d.428 (97)
      About iron at his smithies and oats for seed. This "lade" (Mary, Queen of Scots?) has been sick. He sends her letters that he received yesterday from Gilbert.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/12nme2
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, Ashton (Aston), Derbyshire, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, ca. 1575?; X.d.428 (98)
      This "lade" is still sick. Asks to be commended to his daughter Talbot.
      http://luna.folger.edu/luna/servlet/s/75a7y6
    - Letter from George Talbot, Earl of Shrewsbury, Sheffield, to Elizabeth Hardwick Talbot, Countess of Shrewsbury, ca. 1575?; X.d.428 (99)